Zack, Arnold Additional Arbitration Files 5620
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files
1970-1978
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zack, Arnold
5620
10 cubic feet
10 linear ft.
Arbitration decisions, reports, pamphlets, correspondence, Records.
5677070
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 28, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 04, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Lawyer, arbitrator, and government official; LLB Yale, 1956, MBA Harvard, 1961, MA Harvard, 1963.
Arnold Marshall Zack is an arbitrator and mediator. Beginning his labor career as a part-time election examiner for the National Labor Relations Board and as a case analyst for the U.S. Wage Stabilization Board (1950-1953), he was also a lecturer in labor economics at Simmons College, Northeastern University (1957-1963); an assistant to Saul Wallen, arbitrator, (1956-1960); director of the Labor-Management Institute of the American Academy of Arbitrators (1966-1968); and has served in various labor-related international posts for the United States government.
Other governmental service includes membership on panels for the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, the Massachusetts Public Employment Relations Board, the New York State Public Employment Relations Board, The New Jersey Public Employment Relations Board, The New York City Office of Collective Bargaining, and The National Mediation Board. Zack is also a panel member of the American Arbitration Association, and has served as the permanent arbitrator for a number of major corporations and unions and for the State of New York and the U.S. Postal Service.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5281: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5512: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5551: Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5659: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5727: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files
Arbitration, Industrial; Zack, Arnold.
5677070
- 1976. A-I (Affiliated-Immigration) (Box 1)
  - Affiliated Foods and Teamsters 229 AAA/Philadelphia 1430 1031 75J, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ALCOA and Officeworkers Vacation vs. RIF, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ALCOA and OPEIU #180 Vacation Payments, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allegany, MD Schools, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Araserv & Hotel Employees #217 AAA/Boston #1130-1387-76, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Associated Grocers and Teamsters 633, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Associated Grocers and Teamster 633 Grievance, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Baltimore County & Tabco Grievance, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Baltimore County & Tabco Grievance, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Baltimore County & Tabco, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Scope and Contents
    June 2, 1976
  - Baltimore County & Tabco Personal Leave, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Baltimore County & Tabco Substitution, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Barnstable Schools AAA/Boston #1139-1524-76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Birdsboro & USS AAA/Philadelphia #1430-1373-75J, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - C&S Wholesale Grocers and Teamsters FMCS #76K08780, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cambridge Screw & IAM #264 AAA/Boston #1130-1467-75, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Chamberlain Manufacturing and UAW #1113 New Bedford, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - City National Printing Co. Bristol, CT., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Continental Screw and UAW, #384 AAA/Boston #1130-0107-76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Dover-Sherbourne Schools, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Essex, Vermont Schools, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    May 27, 1976
  - First Mortgage Investors and Hotel 21 AAA/BOS #1130-1099-76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - First National, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    May 3, 1976
  - First National & #592 Discharge, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Steelworkers AAA/BOS #1130-1836-75, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Gorton's & Seafood Workers #15, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Gorton's II, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Haverhill Gas & USS, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - US Immigration and National Border Patrol FMCS #76K11022, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    1970-1973
- 1976. I-N (ITT-Northwest) (Box 2)
  - Kent County, MD, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - I.T.T. and Bakery Workers #348 AAA/Boston # Equalization of Overtime, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Puerto Rico: USDL, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Nov. 29, 1976
  - Lake Region Union HS Orleans, VT, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Leland and Gray High School and VEA, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Metropolitan Life and Insurance Workers AAA/BOS #1130-0578-77, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Middletown, CT Board of Education AAA/Hartford #1239 0068 76, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - MIT & Service Employees, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - MSAD #36 Livermore Falls Schools, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - New England and Power IBEW #326, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Newman-Crosby Steel and USW #3333, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Northrop and UAW #1596 AAA/Boston #1130-0737-76, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - NWA and Teamsters, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    February 11, 1976
  - Northwest and Alpha Surface Deadheading, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    November 23, 1976
  - Northwest and Teamsters Toyko Bed Case 76-8-CAS, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Northwest and ALPA, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    August 23-24, 1976
  - NWA and BRAC- Helena T/A, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Northwest and BRAC, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    October 10, 1976
- 1976. N-S (Northwest-Stroehmann) (Box 3)
  - Northwest and ALPA, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    April 1,1976
  - Northwest and ALPA NWA-329-75, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    March 17, 1976
  - Northwest and ALPA, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    July 27-28,1976
  - Okonite and Boilermakers #745 AAA/Boston #1130-1348-76, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Orange,Vermont Schools AAA/Boston #1139-0548-76, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Procter and Gamble and IOCW, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Scott Graphics and IAM #1544 FMCS#76K23991, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Seafood Kitchens, Gloucester Amalgamated Meatcutters, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Seafood Kitchens and Seafood District 15, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Springfield Transit and Transit 1249 AAA/Chicago 5130 0536 76, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Stanley Plating and UAW #1251 AAA/Hartford #1230-0138-76, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Stop and Shop and Retail Clerks #1325 AAA/Boston #1130-1372-76, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Stop and Shop Security Watchmen AAA/Boston #1130-0855-76, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Stowe,VT Fact-Finding, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    May 1976
  - Stroehmann Bros. and Teamsters #463 AAA/Philadelphia 1430 1265 75J, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- 1976. U-Y (United States-Yale) (Box 4)
  - U.S. Lines and MEBA, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - USPO and NALC #NC-N-389, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - USPO and APWU AB-N-!0,299D AB-N-10, 300D, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - US Postal and NALC NB-N-6474-D, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Lambert 9/23/76
  - USPO & NALC NB-N-6965D, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    September 22, 1976
  - USPO and NALC #NC-N-269: Medina, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - USPO & NALC NC-N-149-D, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    McMamis July 21, 1976
  - USPO & NALC NB-N-6828-D, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Paulides July 13, 1976
  - USPO & NALC #NC-N-880-D, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Roderick July 1, 1976
  - US Postal and APWU AB-N-999T D, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - US Postal and APWU AB-N-10, 193-D, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Jensen March 18, 1976
  - US Postal and NALC NB-N-6473D Finn, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    January 23, 1976
  - USPO & NALC NC-N-197, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Jackson October 6, 1976
  - USPO & NALC NB-N_4817D, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Lindsey January 14,1976
  - West Haven Board of Education & Teachers AAA/Hartford #1239 0024 76, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - West Haven Board of Education & Teachers AAA/Hartford #1329-0119076, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - OF Wilmington & AFSCME AAA/PHIL #1430 0910 75S, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Windham, Vermont, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Worcester Pressed Steel & United Steelworkers: AAA/Boston #1130-1146-74, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Yale Univerisyt Federation of University Employees Holiday Pay, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Welding Engineers & USWA AAA/Philadelphia, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- 1977. A-B (Allegheny-Borden) (Box 5)
  - Associated Grocers Termination, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Associated Grocers and Teamsters Suspension, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Baltimore City Board. Grievance TABCO, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Board of Education Baltimore County and TABCO Grievance, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Board of Education Baltimore County and TABCO Grievance., 1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Baltimore County and TABCO, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    September 23, 1977
  - Baltimore County and TABCO, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Borden and ICWU #553, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Pittsburgh Transit, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- 1977. B-H (Borden-Hudson) (Box 6)
  - British Airways SBA +1/74:, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - British Airways and IAM, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Canada Dry and Distillery Workers AAA/Boston #1130-1024-77, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Canon City, Colorado, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Chelmsford and IBPO #311 AAA/Boston #1139-0103-77, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts AFSCME & #CA-38, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    December 20, 1977
  - Commonwealth Gas and USS AAA/Boston 1130-0520-77, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Connecticut Light and Power AAA/Hartford #1230-0102-77, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Danvers and AFSCME, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - EMHART MFG & UAW #376 AAA/Hartford #1230-0043-77, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Handy & Harmon and Steelworkers AAA/Hartford #1230-0091-77, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Hudson Schools AAA/Boston #1139-0123-77, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- 1977. J-N (John-Northwest) (Box 7)
  - John Hancock and Insurance Workers AAA/Philadelphia #1430-0864-76Q, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Laconia Needle Manufacturing Co, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Manchester Fire Dept. & Local 856 AAA/Boston #1139-1752-76, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Mobil Oil & OCAW #8-831 AAA/Philadelphia #1430-0693-77, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Monadnock Region Fact-finding, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Narragansett Wire & IBEW #1542 AAA/Boston #1130-0030-77, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - NYC Board of Education & Supervisors & Administrators AAA/NYC #1339-1954-76, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Northwest & BRAC, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    October 18-19, 1977
  - Northwest & ALPA, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    January 11, 1977
  - Northwest Airlines and Teamsters, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Domestic Flying July 27, 1977
  - Northwest, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    July 27-28,1997
  - Northwest & Teamsters, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    October 5, 1977
  - Northwest Airlines Teamsters-Seattle NWA76-12 Scheduleing, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Northwest and IBT Last Trip of Month, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    October 29-30, 1977
  - Northwest & ALPA, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    May 4-5,1977
  - Northwest & BRAC, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    March 23-24, 1977
  - Northwest & ALPA Late cancellation, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    March 23,1977
  - Northwest & BRAC Greivance., 1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    March 16, 1977
- 1977. N-P (Northwest-Providence) (Box 8)
  - Northwest & BRAC Controllers vs. Coordinators, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    February 15-16, 1977
  - Northwest & ALPA, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    May 17, 1977
  - PAN AM, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Penn Electric & IBEW U-12, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Penn Power & IBEW AAA/Philadelphia #1430-1565-77J, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    January 5, 1977
  - Boilermakers, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Ogden Food Service & Hotel Employees AAA/Boston #1130-0705-77, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Package Machinery & IUE #220 FMCS #77K04895, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Package Machinery #1, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Polaroid Corporation, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Providence Schools AAA/Boston #1139-0428-76, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- 1977. P-U (Public-United States) (Box 9)
  - Public welfare & SEIU #509 AAA/Boston #1139-0173-77, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - AAA/Boston #1139-1782-76 Public Welfare & SEIS #509, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Pueblo School #60 AAA/DAL #7139-0086-77, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Saugus Schools AAA/BOS #1139-1855-76, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Schaefer & Cement Workers Clerical Interest Arbitration., 1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Seaboard & ALPA NY-118-76, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Smithfield Schools AAA/Boston #1139-1891-76, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Social Security Division FMCS #77K 08626, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Strathmore Paper & UPIU #197 AAA/Boston #1130-1878-76, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Time & Newspaper Guild of NYC, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Tuttle & Bailey & UAW #1251 AAA/Hartford #1230-0279-77, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - USPO & NALC: NC-N-3149-D, NC-N-3150-D, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    January 19, 1977
  - United States Postal & APWU AC-N677SD, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    February 1, 1977
  - USPO & APWU: AC-N-7647D, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    February 11, 1977
  - USPO & APWU: AC-N-9563, AC-N-9564, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    February 2, 1977
  - USPO & APWU AC-N-10, 241-D, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    April 4, 1977
  - USPO & APWU AC-N-10; 417-D, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    May 9, 1977
  - USPO & APWU: AC-N-14; 745D, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    July 21, 1977
  - USPO & NALC AC-N-5288-D-, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    June 22, 1977
  - USPO & APWU AC-N-11, 011-D, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    June 7, 1977
  - USPO & APWU AC-N-6609-D, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    March 1, 1977
  - USPO & APWU AC-N-11,978D, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    July 20, 1977
  - USPO & APWU AC-N-16,541-D, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    September 19, 1977
  - USPO & APWU AC-N-8073-D, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    March 2, 1977
  - USPO & NALC AC-N-18,476-D, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    October 4, 1977
  - USPO & NRLCA RC-N-0259-D, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    November 1, 1977
  - USPO & NALC NC-N-7026-D, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    October 25, 1977
- 1977. V-W (Valley-Wheeler). Also includes 3 transcripts of proceedings involving the Port Authority of Allegheny County and Division 85, Amalgamated Transit Union. (Box 10)
  - Wheeler Manufacturing & USWA AAA/Boton #1130-1661-77, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Western Massachusetts Electric & IBEW #455, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Western Airlines and BRAC Grievance, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    April 1977
  - Western Airlines and BRAC Grievance, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    April 7, 1977
  - Western Airlines * BRAC, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Wayland School Committee AAA/Boston #1139-0868-77, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Valley Gas & Lamp; Utility Workers 472, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 7)